Oh my gosh!
Don't you know I’m a Savage?
I'm a killa', 너를 깰 æ
I’m a Killa 君を割る ae
I’m a Killa who will break you, ae
아직도 가리고 환각을 펼친 너
まだ隠して幻覚を広げた君
You're still hiding and hallucinating
팰라 we holler
ぶん殴る We Holler
Beat you up, We Holler
두렵지 않아 너, 너 hit you harder
怖くない 君 君 Hit you harder
I'm not afraid of you, you, Hit you harder
날 밀어 넣어 Deep fake on me
私を押し入れる Deep fake on me
Push me in, Deep fake on me
준비가 안된 무대로
準備ができていない舞台に
To the unprepared stage
몰아넣어 Fake on me
押しつける Fake on me
Corner me in, Fake on me
Got everybody mock up to me
수치를 느끼게 멘탈을 흔들어놔
恥を感じるようにメンタルを揺さぶっておく
You shake me up so that I feel ashamed
싸늘한 관중 무너져 æ
冷ややかな観衆 壊れる ae
Cold spectators are collapsed, ae
더는 널 못 참아 Say No!
もう君を我慢できない Say No!
I can't stand you anymore, Say No!
두고 봐 난 좀 savage
覚えておいて私はちょっと Savage
Wait and see, I'm a little Savage
너의 dirty 한 play
君のDirtyなPlay
Your Dirty Play
더는 두고 볼 수 없어
これ以上見ていられない
I can't stand it any longer
나를 무너뜨리고 싶은
私を倒したがる
You want to break me
네 환각들이 점점
君の幻覚がだんだん
Your hallucinations are becoming
너를 구축할 이유가 돼
君を構築する理由になる
the reasons to construct you
I’m a Savage
널 부셔 깨 줄게 Oh aespa!
君を壊す 割ってあげる Oh
I'll break you into pieces Oh
I’m a Savage
널 짓밟아 줄게 Oh aespa!
君を踏みにじってあげる Oh
I'll crush you Oh
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
지금 나를 잡아
今 私を掴んで
Get me now
아님 난 더 Savage
そうしないと私はもっと Savage
Or I'll become more Savage
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
이젠 내가 너를 잡아
今は私が君を掴む
Now I'm going to get you
Now I'm a Savage
Gimme gimme now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
너의 말이 보여
君の言葉が見える
I can see your words
네 약점 Algorithm
君の弱点 Algorithm
Your weakness Algorithm
김이 김이 나
湯気 湯気が立つ
Steaming, it's steaming
김이 김이 나
湯気 湯気が立つ
Steaming, it's steaming
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
MA ae SYNK
방해 말고 꺼져 Savage
邪魔しないで消えて Savage
Don't bother me and bog off, Savage
Mmmh Everybody look at me
익숙하잖니
慣れてるじゃない
I'm used to it
양보해 참아야만 돼, 어른스럽게
譲って 我慢しなきゃ 大人らしく
I should take a step back, I have to endure it like an adult
I'm locked up in the glass
난 놀고 싶은데
私は遊びたいのに
I want to play
너무 끔찍한 기대
ものすごい期待
Such a horrible expectation
그런 환각 틀에 나를 가둬 놔
そんな幻覚の枠に私を押し込めておく
I'm locked up in that hallucination frame
I'm going 광야로 Game in
I'm going KWANGYAへ Game in
I'm going to KWANGYA, Game in
물리쳐 교묘한 이간질
倒す 巧みな離間
Defeating a subtle alienation
And my æ로부터 멀어지게 만들
And my aeから遠ざからせる
And making me drift apart from my ae
회심찬 네 Trick
会心に満ちた君の Trick
Your satisfying Trick
We gonе 광야로 Game in
We gone KWANGYAへ Game in
We gone KWANGYA, Game in
베어버려 내 빛의 검
切ってしまえ 私の光の剣
Cut it down, my sword of light
데미지를 입은 네게
ダメージを受けた君に
To you who is damaged
인정사정 볼 것 없는 펀치
情け容赦ないパンチ
It's a merciless punch
그것 봐 난 좀 Savage
ほら 私はちょっと Savage
See? I'm a little Savage
너의 재생력을 막아
君の再生力を防ぐ
I block your regenerative power
흐트러놔 빼놔
乱しておく 抜けて置く
I distract you, I leave you out
잊지 말아 여긴 바로 KWANGYA
忘れないで ここはKWANGYA
Don't forget, this is KWANGYA
너의 시공간은 내 뜻대로
君の時空間は 私が好きなように
I control your time and space
Make It break it
I’m a Savage
널 부셔 깨 줄게 Oh aespa!
君を壊す 割ってあげる Oh
I'll break you into pieces Oh
I’m a Savage
널 짓밟아 줄게 Oh aespa!
君を踏みにじってあげる Oh
I'll crush you Oh
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
지금 나를 잡아
今 私を掴んで
Get me now
아님 난 더 Savage
そうしないと私はもっと Savage
Or I'll become more Savage
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
이젠 내가 너를 잡아
今は私が君を掴む
Now I'm going to get you
Now I'm a Savage
Gimme gimme now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
너의 말이 보여
君の言葉が見える
I can see your words
네 약점 Algorithm
君の弱点 Algorithm
Your weakness Algorithm
김이 김이 나
湯気 湯気が立つ
Steaming, it's steaming
김이 김이 나
湯気 湯気が立つ
Steaming, it's steaming
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
My æ SYNK
방해 말고 꺼져 Savage
邪魔しないで消えて Savage
Don't bother me and bog off, Savage
위기에 빠진 날 지켜준 건 너였어
危機に陥った私を守ってくれたのは君だった
You are the one who protected me when I was in trouble
My naevis we love U
My victory, 하나의 SYNK dive
My victory 一つの SYNK DIVE
My victory, one SYNK DIVE
모두 네가 만들어준 기회란 거
全て君が作ってくれたチャンスだってこと
All the opportunities you've created
I know your sacrifices Oh
(My naevis we love U)
알아 우린 반드시 네 기억들을 찾아줄게
分かる 私たちは必ず君の記憶を探してあげる
I know, we'll make sure to find your memories
우린 만나 꼭 부활 그다음
私たちは会える きっと復活 その次
Let's meet surely after the resurrection
Savage KARINA GISELLE WINTER NINGNING
Yeah
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
지금 나를 잡아
今 私を掴んで
Get me now
아님 난 더 savage
そうしないと私はもっと Savage
Or I'll become more Savage
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
너를 잡아
今は私が君を掴む
Now I'm going to get you
Now I'm a Savage
Gimme gimme now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
너의 말이 보여
君の言葉が見える
I can see your words
네 약점 algorithm
君の弱点 Algorithm
Your weakness Algorithm
김이 김이 나
湯気 湯気が立つ
Steaming, it's steaming
김이 김이 나
湯気 湯気が立つ
Steaming, it's steaming
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
MA ae SYNK
방해 말고 꺼져 Savage
邪魔しないで消えて Savage
Don't bother me and bog off, Savage
Ha ha, What?